Lesson 1. A Puma at large. Pumas are large. Cat-like animals which are found in America.
第1课。彪马很大。在美国发现的类似猫的动物。
spot: v.   看出，发现
When reports came into London zoo that a wild Puma had been spotted 45 miles south of London.
当有报道说，伦敦动物园说，在伦敦以南45英里处发现了一个野生美洲狮。
evidence: n.   证据, accumulate: v.   积累，积聚
They were not taken seriously. However, as the evidence began to accumulate, experts from the zoo
他们没有被认真对待。但是，随着证据开始积累，动物园的专家
oblige: v.   使……感到必须
felt obliged to investigate. For the descriptions given by people who claimed to have seen the Puma
感到有义务进行调查。对于自称看过彪马的人的描述
hunt: n.   追猎；寻找
were extraordinarily similar. The hunt for the Puma began in a small village where a woman
非常相似。对彪马的追捕始于一个小村庄，一个女人
picking blackberries saw a large cat. Only five yards away from her. It immediately ran away
采摘黑莓看到了一只大猫。离她只有五码远。它立即逃跑了
when she saw it, and experts confirmed that a Puma will not attack a human being unless it is
当她看到它时，专家确认，除非是
corner: v.   使走投无路，使陷入困境
cornered. The search proved difficult. For the Puma was often observed at one place in the morning
拐弯。搜索证明很困难。因为在早上经常在一个地方观察到彪马
trail: n.   一串，一系列
and at another place 20 miles away. In the evening, wherever it went, it left behind at a trail
在20英里外的另一个地方。晚上，无论走到哪里，都留在一条小径上
print: n.   印痕
of dead deer and small animals like rabbits. Popprints were seen in a number of places and Puma
死去的鹿和小动物，例如兔子。在多个地方和美洲狮都看到了流行型
cling: v.   粘
fur was found clinging to bushes. Several people complained of cat-like noises at night and a
发现皮毛紧贴灌木丛。几个人在晚上抱怨猫般的声音，一个
convince: v.   使……信服
businessman on a fishing trip saw the. Puma up a tree, the experts were now fully convinced that
商人在钓鱼之旅中看到了。Puma上一棵树，专家现在完全确信
the animal was a Puma. But where had it come from? As no Puma's had been reported missing from any zoo
动物是赤褐色。但是它来自哪里？因为没有puma据报道任何动物园缺少
somehow: adv. 不知怎么搞地，不知什么原因
in the country. This one must have been in the possession of a private collector and somehow
在国家。这一定是一个私人收藏家，并以某种方式拥有
hunt: n.   追猎；寻找, disturb: v.   令人不安
managed to escape. The hunt went on for several weeks. But the Puma was not caught. It is disturbing
设法逃脱。狩猎持续了几个星期。但是没有抓住美洲狮。这令人不安
to think that a dangerous wild animal is still at large in the quiet countryside.
认为危险的野生动物在安静的乡村仍然很大。